e-centives.com 2013-06-23

# CouponNetwork.com Privacy Policy | Consumer Support

### **CouponNetwork.com Privacy Policy**

Effective Date: February 20, 2013

Catalina Marketing Corporation and its subsidiaries (“Catalina ” or “we” or “us”) are dedicated to providing shopper-driven communications, developed and distributed for consumer packaged goods manufacturers, pharmaceutical manufacturers, marketers and retailers (collectively, “clients”). Under the CouponNetwork brand, Catalina provides certain promotional offer and other services and benefits to consumers. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected at or in connection with couponnetwork.com and the CouponNetwork program, and other web sites operated by Catalina where this Privacy Policy is posted (collectively, “the Sites”). This Privacy Policy explains what information is collected on the Sites, how we use your information, and your choices. It does not apply to information Catalina might collect at other Catalina websites, including catalinamarketing.com; that we collect from our international web sites, such as catalinamarketing.it; information we collect through our client relationships, which are typically governed by contract with each client; or information we might collect in other forums, including offline, by email, or by text message.

For information collected offline through our client relationships, please note that we do not collect or store names, email addresses, street addresses or phone numbers. For more information about information collected offline through our client relationships, please visit our Privacy Policy at <http://www.catalinamarketing.com/about/privacy-policy/>

**MODIFICATIONS TO THIS POLICY**

To the extent required by law, we will attempt to notify you of material changes to this Privacy Policy, including by posting the most recent version of the Privacy Policy and information about the changes from the previous version on the Sites. We will post the most recent effective date on the Privacy Policy.  Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, as your use of the Sites indicates to us that you have read and accept our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Policy. In addition, please review our [Terms of Use](http://support.catalinamarketing.com/terms/) which govern your use of the Sites. By providing us with information and by using the Sites, you consent to have your information used as described in this Privacy Policy and you agree to adhere to the Terms.

**COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

We collect and maintain a variety of personally identifiable information in connection with our operation of the Sites and the CouponNetwork program, including, for instance, your name, ZIP Code, email addresses, phone numbers, as well as demographic information. We collect information directly from you, for example through online registration forms for our CouponNetwork program, including your favorite stores, frequent shopping account numbers.  We may also collect information about the coupons you select, print or redeem and this may be associated with your profile information. If you participate in a survey or sweepstakes we may collect your full address, telephone number and date of birth or other eligibility or qualifying information. We may also collect information when you link to or connect from your social media site, such as Facebook.  We may combine the information you provide with additional information we may have about you (for example, information we have obtained through our client relationships), or that may be shared with us by third parties (for example, stores with whom you hold a loyalty card). This information may include purchase preferences.

In addition, we gather information about you that is automatically collected by our web server, such as your IP address and domain name. Your browser also provides us the web site you come from (known as the referring URL), the type of browser and computer you use, the time and date of access, and other information that does not personally identify you.

**COOKIES**

Cookies and log files are technologies used by the Sites to identify a user as he/she moves through our Sites. Your browser allows us to place some information (session based IDs and/or persistent cookies) on your computer’s hard drive that identifies the computer you are using. We may use cookies to personalize our Sites and to track your usage across other sites. Your Web browser can be set to allow you to control whether you will accept cookies, reject cookies, or to notify you each time a cookie is sent to you. If your browser is set to reject cookies, Web sites that are cookie-enabled will not recognize you when you return to the Web site, and some Web site functionality may be lost. The Help section of your browser will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting cookies. Pixel tags, sometimes called Web beacons, are similar in function to a cookie. But because of their insignificant size, it is not visible; though, they may be used to pass certain information to our servers to personalize our Sites and to track your usage across other of our Sites. In addition, we may also use pixel tags in our HTML based e-mails.

We may associate your personally identifiable information with cookies or other tracking utilities our Site places on your computer’s hard drive. Associating a cookie with your contact data allows us to offer increased personalization and functionality. Without cookies, this functionality would not be possible. From time to time, we may use tracking mechanisms such as cookies or web beacons to observe your behavior across multiple websites. We share the information we gather with third parties who serve targeted advertisements to you based on your browsing behaviors. These advertisements are served to you on multiple third party websites. Additionally, on the Sites, there may be certain third-party advertisers whose advertisements contain cookies that collect data from you. Some of those cookies may contain tracking mechanisms that observe your behavior across multiple Sites. Catalina does not control the use of cookies by advertisers or third parties displaying data on the Sites or on the sites you visit using links from the Sites. We and some of our vendors may use DART cookies, a DoubleClick product, which you can opt out of by visiting http://www.doubleclikc.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx.

**USE, SHARING, AND RETENTION OF INFORMATION**

We use personally identifiable information for our general commercial purposes including the purposes described at the time of collection or as otherwise described to you and to process requests. For instance, when you identify your favorite stores, your information is collected by and can be used by Catalina in accordance with this Privacy Policy and by the stores you identify in accordance with their privacy policies.  We also use your information, as permitted by law, to provide you with information about Catalina. CouponNetwork, other of our brands or products and services, our partners’ and/or clients’ products and services, or other product and services in which we believe you may be interested, or for other legitimate Catalina business purposes. If you have enrolled in our Savings Insider feature we will use your email to contact you with information about special offers, coupons or tips.  We may also use your personally identifiable information, or other information we maintain about you (including information we obtain or gather about your purchase preferences) to tailor your experience at the Sites; to compile, display and/or provide you with content, coupons, offers or other information in which we think you might be interested; as requested or required by our business partners which may include for their marketing purposes; or as otherwise permitted by law. We also gather aggregate data about visitors to our Sites for market analysis.

We may provide information from our Sites in aggregate form, with identifying information removed, to third parties. Please note that with respect to any personal information such third parties may collect from you independent of us and outside the scope of Sites maintained by us on our servers, we will have no control over the use of such information by such third parties and the use and gathering of such data will be subject to the third parties’ privacy policies on the respective web sites.

When you visit our Sites there may be an opportunity for you to participate in one or more surveys. Your participation in any survey is completely voluntary. During the survey, we may ask you to provide basic contact information in addition to responding to the questions within the survey itself. Many of our surveys will include the opportunity to earn prizes for participating. If you win one of the prizes, we may share your contact information with a third party for fulfillment and delivery of your prize.

In addition, we may share personally identifiable information with third parties for legitimate business purposes, including for the following reasons or in the following circumstances:

Companies and people who work for us: Because we are a large company, we contract with other companies and individuals to help us provide services. For example, we may host some of our websites on another company’s computers, hire technical consultants to maintain our applications, or work with companies to analyze data, provide marketing assistance, and provide customer service. These other companies may have access to some of the personal information we maintain about our users or employees. Other companies may collect information on our behalf through their sites. This occasionally incorporates the use of frames on the Sites that will not show the URL you are visiting in the browser address window.

Promotional and informational offers: Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of shoppers. To accomplish this we may use third parties working on behalf of Catalina.

Business transfers: We may share personally identifiable information in anticipation of and in the course of an actual or potential sale, reorganization, consolidation, merger, or amalgamation of all or part of our business or operations.

Legal purposes: We may share personal information when we believe it is necessary to cooperate with law enforcement or in response to a government request, including if specifically requested or required, as otherwise permitted by law, to investigate potentially fraudulent or questionable activities, and for other valid Catalina business purposes.

We also may use your personal information on an aggregated basis to provide third parties with information, such as to help us develop new features and content for the Sites, and to provide others with aggregate information about our users and the usage patterns of the Sites.

We retain personally identifiable information for as long as necessary for its legitimate business purposes, and as otherwise permitted by applicable law.

**SECURITY**

We use reasonable measures to safeguard sensitive personally identifiable information, which measures are appropriate to the type of information maintained, and follows applicable laws regarding safeguarding any such information under our control.

We cannot guarantee, however, that your information will remain secure. The Internet by its nature is a public forum, and we encourage you to use caution when disclosing information online. Often, you are in the best situation to protect yourself online. You are responsible for protecting your username and password from third party access, and for selecting passwords that are secure.

**LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES**  
  
From time to time, we will provide links to third-party web sites, or advertisements will contain links to third-party sites. For example, we may link to a third party who is assisting in or is providing online training services. These links are provided as a service to you. These sites are operated by independent entities that have their own privacy policies. This Privacy Policy does not apply to such other sites or to the use that those entities make of your information. Catalina has no control over the content displayed on such sites, nor over the measures, if any, that are taken by such sites to protect the privacy of your information.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS** If you have an established business relationship with us and are a California resident, under California law you may request from us a list of the categories of personal information we have disclosed to third parties for those third parties’ marketing purposes, and a list of the third parties to whom we have shared that information. We will include in that list the names and addresses of the third parties who received the information and used it (or who we believe may have used it) for their own marketing purposes.

To exercise your rights, you may make one request each year by sending an email to [Shine the Light@ catalinamarketing.com](mailto:shinethelight@catalinamarketing.com) Indicate in your email that you are making a “Shine the Light” inquiry. Responses to requests sent to this email address will be provided within 30 days.

**HOW TO CONTACT US AND MODIFY YOUR INFORMATION OR PREFERENCES**

You can always contact us in order to (i) update the personal information that you have provided to us, and (ii) change your preferences with respect to marketing contacts by using [this form](http://support.catalinamarketing.com/?cn) or if available also logging into your account to update your information. If you would like to modify the types of marketing email or text messages you receive from us, you may do so by following the instructions within the body of any email or text message that you receive from us, or as instructed in the program terms (such as the [CouponNetwork Program Terms](http://support.catalinamarketing.com/terms/)).

If you have any other questions about our Privacy Policy, or our Safe Harbor commitments under EU-US Safe Harbor or Switzerland-US Safe Harbor programs, please feel free to contact us through one of our Sites, email us at privacy@catalinamarketing.com, or write to us at:

Chief Privacy Officer  
c/o Catalina Corporation  
200 Carillon Parkway  
St. Petersburg, FL 33716 USA

**CHILDREN**

Our Sites are intended for a general audience and are not intended for use by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from any visitor under the age of 13, and we strive to comply with the provisions of COPPA (The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). If you are a parent of a child under 13, and you believe that your child has provided us with information about him or herself, please contact us at privacy@catalinamarketing.com. ** **

**US/EU SAFE HARBOR – US/SWITZERLAND SAFE HARBOR**

Catalina Corporation is a participant in the Safe Harbor program developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union and Switzerland. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles with regard to our use of employee, shopper, and other personal information. For more information about the Safe Harbor and to view our certification, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Safe Harbor Web site (<http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>).

CouponNetwork Privacy Policy created and updated on February 20, 2013.
